(Raj:)is only a year away.
(Raj:)A lot of the things in that
movie haven't been invented yet.
(Leonard:)How cool would that be
(Leonard:)if we could make
one of those a reality?
(Sheldon:)If we could figure out
the scientific basis
(Sheldon:)for Marty's hover board,
(Sheldon:)that would have
universal application.
Well, it's-it's possible
at absolute zero,
(Leonard:)but we would
have to remove
(Leonard:)the temperature restrictions.
(Raj:)Oh, I have an idea.
(Sheldon:)I think I have the same one.
(Howard:)We got to watch
Back to the Future II!
(Raj:)I'll make the popcorn.
(Penny:)So, where should
we go first?
(Raj:)Ooh.
(Amy:)There's a cover band
in the lounge.
(Penny:)Nah.
But they play Barry Manilow.
(Howard:)No.
But they're called
"Fairly Manilow."
(Penny:)Oh. Okay.
Great!
No!
(Bernadette:)Well, what do you want
to do?
(Penny:)Well, we're in Vegas.
(Penny:)I want to go downstairs,
get a bucket of margaritas,
(Penny:)dance until I vomit
all over a roulette wheel
(Penny:)and watch it go everywhere.
(Amy:)What if we don't want to vomit?
(Penny:)Oh, you will. That's why
they give you the bucket.